A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, General Correspondence FA735
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1959
  - CA – CZ [General File]: Cronin – CZ, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - California…, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - California, University of (Berkeley), 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - California, University of (Los Angeles), 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Cambridge University, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Camp…, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Canada…, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Canadian…, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - CARE, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Carleton College, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Carroll, Thomas., 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Carter…, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Casey, R.G., 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Catholic…, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Carrie Chapman Catt Memorial Fund Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Center…, 1959 (Reel C-1316)
  - Centre d'Etudes Industrialles, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Ceylon, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Chein, Isidor, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Chicago…, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Chicago, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Children's, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Chile, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Chile, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - China, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Christian…, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Church Peace Union, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Cincinnati Council on World Affairs, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Clark…, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Cleveland, Harlan, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Cohen…, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - Colgate University, 1959 (Reel C-1317)
  - College…, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Colombia…, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Colorado…, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Colorado State University, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Colorado, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Committee…, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Committee for International Economic Growth, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Committee for the Study of Mankind, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Community…, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Council…, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Conference Board of Associated research Councils, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Conferences for Corporation Executives, 1959 (Reel C-1318)
  - Connecticut, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - Cornell University, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - Costa Rica, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - Council on Higher Education in the American Republics, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - Council for International Progress in Management, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
    File missing since October 30, 1974; not microfilmed.
  - Council on Social Work Education, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - Crane…, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - DA – DZ [General File]: DA – De Voe, 1959 (Reel C-1319)
  - DA – DZ [General File]: De Voe – DZ, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Dakar University, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Dale, Ernest, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Dartmouth University, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Davies…, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Davis…, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Detroit Institute of Technology, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Delhi, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Doxiadis Associates, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Duke University, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - Duquesne University, 1959 (Reel C-1320)
  - EA – EZ [General File], 1959 (Reel C-1321)
  - Edison Foundation Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1321)
  - Education Research Council of greater Cleveland, 1959 (Reel C-1321)
  - Egypt, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - Elliot…, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - Enke, Stephen, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - Epstein, Albert, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - Ernst, Morris L., 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - European…, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - European Institute of Business Administration, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - European Productivity Agency, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - Evangelical Confederation of Columbia, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - Evans…, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - Exchange of Persons, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - FA – FZ [General File]: FA – Flynt, 1959 (Reel C-1322)
  - FA – FZ [General File]: Flynt – FZ, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Far West Slavic Association, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Far Western Slavic Conference, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Feder, Ernest, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Federation, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Finland, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - First, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Fisher, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Florida, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Florida State University, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Florida, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Food and Agricultural Organization, 1959 (Reel C-1323)
  - Ford…, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Fordham University, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Foreign…, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Frank…, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Franklin Publications Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Fraser…, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Free…, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Free Europe Committee, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - French…, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - Fund for Dental Education, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - GA – GZ [General File]: GA – Gitre, 1959 (Reel C-1324)
  - GA – GZ [General File]: Gitre – GZ, 1959 (Reel C-1325)
  - Gallaudet College, 1959 (Reel C-1325)
  - Gant, George F., 1959 (Reel C-1325)
  - Garnsey, Morris E., 1959 (Reel C-1325)
  - General…, 1959 (Reel C-1325)
  - Ginsburg, Norton, 1959 (Reel C-1325)
  - Girls Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - Goddard College, 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - Gordon…, 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - Great…, 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - Greater…, 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - Green…, 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - Guatemala, 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - HA – HZ [General File]: HA – Henderlider, 1959 (Reel C-1326)
  - HA – HZ [General File]: Henderlider – HZ, 1959 (Reel C-1327)
  - Haffkine Institute, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hall, Hamilton, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hane, Edward, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Harvard University, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hauser, Philip, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hawaii, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hazard, Leland, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hazen Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Heald, Henry T., 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Health and Welfare Council, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Health and Welfare Council of Indianapolis and Marion County, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hear Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Henry…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Herkovits, Melville J., 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hill…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hill, F.F., 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hill Family Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hispanic Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hobbs…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hoffman…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Holy…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Horikawa, Takeo, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Houle, Cyril O., 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Howard…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Howe…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hudson…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Humanities Center for Liberal Education, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Humphreys…, 1959 (Reel C-1328)
  - Hunt…, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Hutchinson, Ralph Cooper, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - IA – IZ [General File], 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Idaho, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Illinois, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Independent…, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - India, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Indian, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Indiana, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Indonesia, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Industrial, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Industrial University of Santander, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Ingersoll…, 1959 (Reel C-1329)
  - Institut…, 1959 (Reel C-1330)
  - Institute…, 1959 (Reel C-1330)
  - Institute for International Order, 1959 (Reel C-1330)
  - Institute for Juvenile Economics (Pakistan), 1959 (Reel C-1330)
  - Institute of International Education, 1959 (Reel C-1330)
  - Instituto…, 1959 (Reel C-1330)
  - Inter-American…, 1959 (Reel C-1330)
  - International…, 1959 (Reel C-1330, Reel C-1331)
  - International Aeronautical Associates, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - International Aeronautical Corporation, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - International Affairs Program (Ford Foundation), 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - International Rice commission, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - International Training and Research (ITR) (For d Foundation), 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - International Training and Research (ITR) Fellowship (January – March), 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - Iowa…, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - Iowa, state University of, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - Israel, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - Istanbul, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - Iverson…, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - Ivory Coast, 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - JA – JZ [General File], 1959 (Reel C-1331)
  - Jackson…, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Japan, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Jencks, Clinton, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Jewish…, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Johnson…, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Johnston…, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Jones…, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Jordan…, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Journal of the Academy of Management, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Joyce, Jean, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - KA – KZ [General File]: KA – Kaznacheev, 1959 (Reel C-1332)
  - KA – KZ [General File]: Kaznacheev – Kubacki, 1959 (Reel C-1333)
  - KA – KZ [General File]: Kubacki – KZ, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kansas, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kansas City, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kansas, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kaplan…, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kelly…, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kennedy…, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kent…, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kentucky, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Khan…, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - King…, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Kirshbaum, Bernard, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - Klein…, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - KPFA (FM) [radio station], Pacifica Foundation, Berkeley, California, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - LA – LZ [General File]: LA – Lerner, 1959 (Reel C-1334)
  - LA – LZ [General File]: Lerner – LZ, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Lake…, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Latin America, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - League of Women Voters, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Learning Resources Institute, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Lebanon, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Lee…, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Leonard…, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Levine…, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Lewis…, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Liberia, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Library of Congress, 1959 (Reel C-1335)
  - Library of International Relations, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Linblad, Bertil, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Lincoln…, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Linnik, Philip S., 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Livingston…, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Lloyd, David D., 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - London, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Long…, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Los Angeles…, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Louisiana…, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Louisiana State University, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - Lunning, Just, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - MA – MZ [General File]: MA – Marris, 1959 (Reel C-1336)
  - MA – MZ [General File]: Marris – Middlesex Hospital, 1959 (Reel C-1337)
  - MA – MZ [General File] Middlesex Hospital – MZ, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Macalester College, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Madrid, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Maine, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Management Development Institute, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Manhattan…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Marine…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Marin…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Maryknoll…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Maryland…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Mason…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Massachusetts…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Matthews…, 1959 (Reel C-1338)
  - Maxson, R.D., 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Mayer…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Metropolitan…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Mexico…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Miami, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Michigan…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Michigan Probate and Juvenile Court Judge Association, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Michigan State University, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Michigan State University (Oakland), 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Michigan, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Midwest College Art Conference, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Miller…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Millikin University, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Milwaukee…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Milwaukee Art Center, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Ministry…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Minnesota…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Missionary…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Mississippi…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Missouri…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Missouri, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Mitchell…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Modern…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Modern Language Association of America, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Monastery…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Monastery of the Infant Jesus (Lufkin, Texas, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Montana…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Moore…, 1959 (Reel C-1339)
  - Moore, Ben T., 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Morgan…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Morris…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Morrison…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Morse…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Moron…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Moss…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Moss, Louis, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Mount…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Mudd College, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Murphy…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Murray…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Museum…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Myers…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - NA – NZ [General File], 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Nash…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - Nathan…, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - The Nation (magazine), re: Ford Foundation - Creative Writers Program, 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - National A... – National Lutheran Council), 1959 (Reel C-1340)
  - National Military-Industrial Conference – National Z, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Academy of Broadcasting, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National of Sciences, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Association, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Conference …, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Council…, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Council on Community Foundations, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Education Association, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Health Council, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Information Bureau, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Planning Association, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - National Science Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - Near East…, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - Nellis, Mary T., 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - Nepal, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - New..., 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - New England Deans of Collegiate Schools of Business, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - New School for Social Research, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - New York…, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - New York City…, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - College of the City of New York, 1959 (Reel C-1341)
  - New York Medical College, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - New York State…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - New York State Education Department, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - New York University, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Newburn, Henry K., 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Nichols…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Nigeria, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Nigerian…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - North…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - North Carolina Junior Science Symposium, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
    File missing since November 18, 1974; not microfilmed.
  - North Carolina, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - North Central Theatre Association, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - North Dakota…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - North Jersey Playhouse, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Northeastern…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Northern…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Northwest…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Northwestern University, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Norton…, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Norton, Frank, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - OA – OZ [General File]: OA – Okullo, 1959 (Reel C-1342)
  - OA – OZ [General File]: Okullo – OZ, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Oak…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Oberlin College, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - O'Brien…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - O'Connell…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - O'Connor…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - O' Donnell…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Office of…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Office of Education, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Ohio, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Ohio State University, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Oklahoma…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Oklahoma, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Opera…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Operations Missions to…, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Oregon, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Organization of American States, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Organization for European Economic Cooperation, 1959 (Reel C-1343)
  - Osborne…, 1959 (Reel C-1344)
  - Our…, 1959 (Reel C-1344)
  - Overseas…, 1959 (Reel C-1344)
  - Overseas Development (Ford Foundation program), 1959 (Reel C-1344)
  - Overseas Development Program Standard Report, 1959 (Reel C-1344)
  - Overseas Development Program Status Report, 1959 (Reel C-1344)
  - Owen…, 1959 (Reel C-1345)
  - Owens…, 1959 (Reel C-1345)
  - Oxford University, 1959 (Reel C-1345)
  - PA – PZ [General File]: PA – Poage, 1959 (Reel C-1345)
  - PA – PZ [General File]: Poage – PZ, 1959 (Reel C-1346)
  - Pacific…, 1959 (Reel C-1346)
  - Pakistan…, 1959 (Reel C-1346)
  - Pakistan, 1959 (Reel C-1346, Reel C-1347)
  - Pakistan Students' Association of America, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pan American…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Parker…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pash, Donald, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Patterson, Frederick D., 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pavia, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pelcovits, N.A., 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pennsylvania…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pepin, Eugene, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Philadelphia Housing Association, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Philippines, University of the, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Phillips…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Polish…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Population…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - President's…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - President's Committee to Study the U.S. Military Assistance Program, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Press Intelligence…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Price…, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Princeton University, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - The Principia, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Pruitt, William O., 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Public Administration Service, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Public Health Service, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - Puerto Rico, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1347)
  - QA – QZ [General File], 1959 (Reel C-1348)
  - RA – RZ [General File]: RA – Rosen, 1959 (Reel C-1348)
  - RA – RZ [General File]: Rosen – RZ, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rapkin, Chester, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Reader's Digest, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Real Estate, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Regional Science Association, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Research Institute of America, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Resources for the Future Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Retinger, J.H., 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd G., 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rice…, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Richards…, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Roberts…, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rogers, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rogers, Frederick Rand, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Roper and Associates, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rose…, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rosenberg Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rosenthal Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1349)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1959 (Reel C-1350)
  - Royal…, 1959 (Reel C-1350)
  - Rutgers University, 1959 (Reel C-1350)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: SA – Secondary Education Board, 1959 (Reel C-1350)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: Secondary Education Board – Spector, 1959 (Reel C-1351)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: Spector – SZ, 1959 (Reel C-1352)
  - Saint…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - San…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - San Francisco State College, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Sanders…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Santa…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Santos, Eduardo, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Saturday Review, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Save the Children Federation, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Schwartz…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Scott…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - SEATO Graduate School of Engineering [Asian Institute of Technology], 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Seattle, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Senate Appropriations Committee, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Sharp, Byron H., 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Shaw, Alice B., 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Sister…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Sisters…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Small…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Smith…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Society…, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - Society for International Development, 1959 (Reel C-1353)
  - South…, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - South Africa, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Southern…., 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Southern California, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Southwestern Social Science Association, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Springfield College, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Standard…, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Stanford University, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - State Department (United States), 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Stevens…., 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Stewart…, 1959 (Reel C-1354)
  - Stone…, 1959 (Reel C-1355)
  - Sutton, Francis X., 1959 (Reel C-1355)
  - Syracuse University, 1959 (Reel C-1355)
  - Syria, 1959 (Reel C-1355)
  - TA – TZ [General File]: TA – Tucker, 1959 (Reel C-1355)
  - TA – TZ [General File]: Tucker – TZ, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Tarneha, Ram, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Taylor…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Technical Assistance Information Clearing House, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Tennessee…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Tennessee, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Texas…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Texas, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Thabit, Walter, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
    File Missing since December, 1974.
  - Thomas…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Thompson…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Three Lion, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Time, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Tinker, Hugh, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Toby, Jackson, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Toman, Walter, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Trinity…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Tufts University, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Tulane University, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Tunisia…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Turkey…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Turner…, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - UA – UZ [General File], 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - UNESCO, 1959 (Reel C-1356)
  - Union…, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United…, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United Arab Republic, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United Community Service of Metropolitan Boston, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United Nations, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United Nations Economic commission for Latin America, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United States, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United States Information Agency, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United States Information Service, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - United States National Commission for UNESCO, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - University…, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - University College…, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - University College of Addis Ababa, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - University College of West Indies, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - UNLA (Community Improvement through Adult Education, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - Urban League of Philadelphia, 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - VA – VZ [General File], 1959 (Reel C-1357)
  - Van…, 1959 (Reel C-1358)
  - Vermont, 1959 (Reel C-1358)
  - Virginia, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1358)
  - Von…, 1959 (Reel C-1358)
  - WA – WZ [General File]: WA – Willcox, 1959 (Reel C-1358)
  - WA – WZ [General File]: Willcox – WZ, 1959 (Reel C-1359)
  - Walker…, 1959 (Reel C-1359)
  - Walker, Hugh W., 1959 (Reel C-1359)
  - Ward…, 1959 (Reel C-1359)